conductexam.in 2017-08-03

# Privacy Policy Conduct Exam

Your privacy is important to us at Conduct Exam. Here is how your Privacy is maintained:

  * We don’t request access to your personal information unless we truly need it to provide the service eg: Your gender or income levels are irrelevant to us, so we don’t ask you for that information.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which adhere to those principles.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please initiate a chat with us, or [send us an email](mailto:info@conductexam.com) at any time.

Conduct exam operates a web application and corresponding mobile apps (on [**www.conductexam.com**](http://www.conductexam.com/home)). It is conduct exam’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our services.

### Website Visitors

Like most internet-service operators, conduct exam collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers, apps and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, geographical location, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Conduct exam’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how conduct exam’s visitors use its services, and to provide conduct exam users the ability to understand how their visitors use their services. From time to time, conduct exam may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its services.

Conduct exam also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users that use the services and visitors.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to conduct exam’s websites and users of conduct exam’s apps choose to interact with conduct exam in ways that require conduct exam to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that conduct exam gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask users of our app to provide an email address. In each case, conduct exam collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with conduct exam. Conduct exam does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

Conduct exam may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, conduct exam does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Conduct exam discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying infrmation only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that:

(i) need to know that information in order to process it on conduct exam’s behalf or to provide services available at conduct exam’s web services, and

(ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country by using conduct exam’s web services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Conduct exam will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, conduct exam discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when conduct exam believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of conduct exam, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of conduct exam and have supplied your email address, conduct exam may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with conduct exam and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Conduct exam takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Conduct exam uses cookies to help conduct exam identify and track visitors, their usage of conduct exam website, and their website access preferences. Conduct exam visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using conduct exam’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of conduct exam’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

If conduct exam, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that conduct exam goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of conduct exam may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by conduct exam and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

Although most changes are likely to be minor, conduct exam may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in conduct exam’s sole discretion. Conduct exam encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of these services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
